

Arthur Menken Emerging & Versatile UX Designer

arthurmenken.nl • +31 683700087 • Email • LinkedIn

Professional Summary

I'm a motivated and emerging UX designer with a broad skill set that includes user research techniques such as conducting interviews, surveys, and usability tests. I have a strong technical foundation and am proficient in using Sketch and Figma to create engaging designs. My recent experience in developing a PC builder feature for Tweakers has taught me the importance of collaborating effectively with developers and stakeholders to bring designs to life that best serve the end user.

Work Experience

UX Design Intern Tweakers

Nov 2022 - Apr 2023 Amsterdam, Netherlands Managed the end-to-end design process of a PC Builder feature for Tweakers, conducting user research, creating wireframes and prototypes, and iteratively testing the design. Designed intuitive user flows, engaging interactions, and an interface in line with the Tweakers brand guidelines. Developed a comprehensive handover package, enabling the team to continue with the project beyond the prototype stage.

UX Design Intern Talpa eCommerce

May 2022 - Oct 2022 Amsterdam, Netherlands Honed mobile-first design skills at Talpa eCommerce, crafting designs for A/B tests, new features, and redesigns using Sketch app. Conducted thorough user research to identify pain points and opportunities for improvement in the customer journey, employing various research methods.

UX Design Intern Tweakers

Sep 2021 - Nov 2021 Amsterdam, Netherlands Designed impactful and creative UX solutions for Tweakers' website, wireframing page redesigns using Figma, and designing and coding A/B test variants for use in Google Optimize and SiteSpect.

Education

Amsterdam University of Applied Sciences

Bachelor of Science in Communication & Multimedia Design

Focused on digital design and interactive product development with a curriculum covering design, technology, and interaction design. The program emphasizes user-centered design to ensure products meet users' needs and includes courses in web design, app development, gaming, and interactive installations. 2018 – 2022

Skills

- UX Design
- Interaction Design
- Prototyping
- User Research
- Figma
- Sketch App
- A/B Testing
- · Front-end Coding

Languages

- · Dutch (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- · German (Rudimentary)